

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Cultivate more experience, job skills and want to confirm the work being done was a professional job.

Learning and development experience working in a modern work environment, fair competition and the opportunity to learn to go further, and contributing to the company precious thrive. Striving with the motto "Have passion for the work will be successful," to become excellent employees of the company and look forward to becoming a long-term contribution to the strong growth of the company

FOLLOW ME

Gmail

ngocthock1994.tn@gmail.com

Contact



+84 938 471 830



C7 Apartment, Man Thien Street, Tang Nhon Phu A Ward, District 9, HCMC

Nguyễn Ngọc Thơ

EDUCATION

MIEN TRUNG INDUSTRY AND COLLEGE

SEP 2012-MAY 2015

- Specialized: Mechanical Engineering
- Diplomas and Certificates:
- Certificate in English Language Arts degree C by Phu Yen University dated 19.12.2014
- Certificate in Computer Arts degree A from Industrial College of Tuy Hoa dated 04.24.2015
- Certificate Soft Skills in Industrial College of Tuy Hoa, dated 10.04.2015
- Certification Mastercam software programming by Industrial College of Tuy Hoa dated 08/04/2014

SKILLS

Hard working

Analytical



Well-organized



EXPERIENCE

SAIGON BEER PHU YEN COMPANY (INTERNSHIP) JUN 2014-OCT 2014

Mechanical maintenance staff:

- Conducting routine inspections of premises and equipment.
- Handling basic repairs and maintenance.
- Repairing machines, equipment, or structures as necessary.



OBJECTIVE

Cultivate more experience, job skills and want to confirm the work being done was a professional job.

Learning and development experience working in a modern work environment, fair competition and the opportunity to learn to go further, and contributing to the company precious thrive. Striving with the motto "Have passion for the work will be successful," to become excellent employees of the company and look forward to becoming a long-term contribution to the strong growth of the company

FOLLOW ME

Gmail

ngocthock1994.tn@gmail.com

Contact



+84 938 471 830



C7 Apartment, Man Thien Street, Tang Nhon Phu A Ward, District 9, HCMC

Nguyễn Ngọc Thơ

EXPERIENCE

NIDEC COPAL PRECISION VIET NAM

Feb 2015-Feb 2016

Maintenance technician:

- Take care Utility, Production line, Process
- Comply with internal rule, VN law in operation & maintenance.
- Analyze machine's breakdowns to find out root cause & carry out improvement to reduce these.
- Improve safty of work & machinery.

SAMSUNG ELECTRONICS HCMC COMPLEX

MAR 2016-MAR 2019

Production Shift Leader:

- April 2016 to May 2016 is trained and work abroad at Samsung Thailand
- Manage a team included 50 peoples assigned for part of production process.
- Ensure effective production operation.
- Manage workers in shift
- Support & report to Production Section Manager & Supervisor such as: production quantity, productivity, machine operation efficiency and working situation of workers.
- Control the team to ensure that production plan is achieved on a daily basis.
- Communicate with other Teams in the process or other processes for adjustment and co-operation.
- Periodically coordinate with the technical department of the plant to implement the maintenance and maintenance of machinery and equipment systems.
- Proposing new technologies, tools and techniques for production lines to improve production efficiency.
- Lead the team / team to overcome challenges to achieve the goals.
- Training and coaching staff on new knowledge, standards and new programs applied in production.



OBJECTIVE

Cultivate more experience, job skills and want to confirm the work being done was a professional job.

Learning and development experience working in a modern work environment, fair competition and the opportunity to learn to go further, and contributing to the company precious thrive. Striving with the motto "Have passion for the work will be successful," to become excellent employees of the company and look forward to becoming a long-term contribution to the strong growth of the company

FOLLOW ME

Gmail

ngocthock1994.tn@gmail.com

Contact



+84 938 471 830



C7 Apartment, Man Thien Street, Tang Nhon Phu A Ward, District 9, HCMC

Nguyễn Ngọc Thơ

EXPERIENCE

AVERY DENNISON RIS VIETNAM

MAR 2019-DEC 2019

Supervisor Production:

- Directly supervises employees in a production site. (2 technical & 55 operators)
- Monitors work, alters schedules to meet unforeseen conditions, controls load factors and flow of work to ensure maximum use of available capacity and effective use of labor, tools and equipment.
- Design and implement operations improvement strategies for safety, cost, quality, training, inventory, and services.
- Analyze and draw information for daily operational needs and improvement for the team.
- Provide prompt problem solving for key issues.
- Responsible for key operational measures within business unit (service, quality, productivity, cost, safety)
- Collaborate with other functional areas to resolve problems and develop improved manufacturing processes. Make efforts to reduce manufacturing waste and process complexity.
- Support & report to Production Manager Operations & Assistant Manager such as: production quantity, productivity, machine operation efficiency and working situation of workers.

INTERESETS

- Watching TV commercials, readbooks, love to travel
- Play sports:football,volleyball,billiards, table tennis
- o Music